The kettle and the idol
I was going to make this the last one.
No, no, no, if I do this, it's going to end with some kind of mumbo-jumbo.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, good.
I love meat and white rice!
Oh!
Yes, sir.
I love meat and rice.
How do you eat rice, for example? Meat?
Well, I basically like to eat yakiniku.
Oh, you love yakiniku?
I love yakiniku.
Oh, good.
I was wondering what you were going to serve.
Oh, my God.
I love barbecue.
You look like a mama idol.
Really?
Yes.
Do you order rice with yakiniku from the start?
From the beginning? When do you order it?
Well, you know, there's a certain way of eating meat, or after eating meat, or...
Then, let's eat meat properly at first.
That too with rice.
Without rice, the meat won't go well.
Really?
Do you go out with the members?
Yes, we do.
And we all go to yakiniku together.
Yakiniku with everyone.
How do you like it?
You eat a lot of meat, don't you?
A lot of food!
That's right.
The money was terrible.
There's money and there's money.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I know you like the high road.
But I like typhoons.
It's the same with barbecue, right?
That's right.
I'm satisfied as long as I can get the top end.
So you think it's important to have Sendai tongue?
It's important.
It's different in your hometown. Take Tokyo's tongue.
It's totally different.
I'd like to know.
Well... there's a difference between yakiniku beef tongue and the kind you get at a beef tongue restaurant.
Beef tongue served at a beef tongue restaurant is different.
They are different.
I really want you to enjoy the difference.
Why do you only eat tan?
Why?
I'm just trying to enjoy it.
I see.
It's true.
You can do that without even knowing it.
You've got it.
What goes best with that meat is white rice.
Yes, white rice.
I don't know what it is.
There's something.
It's called Date Masamu.
There's a rice from Miyagi called Date Masamu.
Once again, how do you promote it?
Are we done with the ambassadors?
I'm not sure.
I haven't gotten any work at all.
There's this rice from Miyagi called Date Masamu.
It's delicious freshly cooked.
Even when it's cold, it's delicious.
Please try it!
Date Masamu
Advertising time!
Nice name!
Date Masamu.
Did you eat it?
Yes, I did.
I used to eat a lot of it back then.
It goes really well with it.
It tastes good even when it's cold.
You can make onigiri (rice balls) and take them with you.
It's wonderful!
It has sweetness.
It's very firm.
I'd like to try it.
It's delicious.
I'll bring some next time.
Thank you very much.
By all means.
We'll have to come to you.
No, no, no, no, I'll bring it.
It's really good... with really good lyrics... and I especially like the chorus.
I don't remember the lyrics.
I don't know...
I'm so happy to meet you, Yusuke.
I'm so happy to meet you, Chanshi!
Yuki-chanYuki-chan
Sent courtesy of DD Keisuke Iginari!
Thank you all!
Thank you